<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing on Austin Repp</title>
    <link>/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing on Austin Repp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How I increased my conversion rate by 2% in a day.</title>
      <link>/increasing-conversion-rate-with-new-landing-page-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/increasing-conversion-rate-with-new-landing-page-trailer/</guid>
      <description>Background My app, Discord Bot Studio , is a visual programming tool for creating chatbots for Discord. The application runs on Desktop, and is distributed on Steam, since that&amp;rsquo;s where my target audience hangs out. The product had been selling decently since its release in May 2020, but I was constantly looking for ways to drive more traffic to it. After trying lots of marketing strategies, to varying degrees of success, I realized that I may be able to increase the number of copies being sold without bringing more people to the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Sales from YouTube micro-influencers</title>
      <link>/youtubemicro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/youtubemicro/</guid>
      <description>For the last few months, I’ve been reaching out to “micro influencers” on YouTube, with the hope of driving targeted traffic to my product, http://discordbotstudio.org. I’m classifying micro influencers as having between 1,000 – 10,000 subscribers on YouTube. The benefit of reaching channels of this size is that they have dedicated audiences based on a certain niche (in my case this is Discord Bots and the creation thereof).
Background Info Discord Bot Studio (DBS) is a visual programming tool I released on Steam on May 12th, 2020 (2 months prior to writing this).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>