<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Austin Repp</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Austin Repp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to fix: Express.js Request Body is Undefined</title>
      <link>/express-js-req-body-undefined/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/express-js-req-body-undefined/</guid>
      <description>express.bodyParser() is no longer bundled with express. You can install it using npm i body-parser.
Fixing the error The code below shows how you can include bodyParser, and by extension jsonParser. Then, simply list jsonParser as the second argument in your POST method, and you will no longer have an undefined request body.
const app = express(); var bodyParser = require(&amp;#34;body-parser&amp;#34;); var jsonParser = bodyParser.json(); // POST /endpoint expects JSON body app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I increased my conversion rate by 2% in a day.</title>
      <link>/increasing-conversion-rate-with-new-landing-page-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/increasing-conversion-rate-with-new-landing-page-trailer/</guid>
      <description>Background My app, Discord Bot Studio , is a visual programming tool for creating chatbots for Discord. The application runs on Desktop, and is distributed on Steam, since that&amp;rsquo;s where my target audience hangs out. The product had been selling decently since its release in May 2020, but I was constantly looking for ways to drive more traffic to it. After trying lots of marketing strategies, to varying degrees of success, I realized that I may be able to increase the number of copies being sold without bringing more people to the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write to a CSV (Excel) file in C</title>
      <link>/how-to-write-to-a-csv-file-in-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-write-to-a-csv-file-in-c/</guid>
      <description>Writing to a CSV using C code A basic CSV file relies on a comma-separated data format, which makes it straightforward to write to this file type from a c program.
First you will want to create a file pointer, which will be used to access and write to a file. Then we call fopen on this file pointer, passing in the name of the file we want to write to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28&#43; free web development resources</title>
      <link>/best-developer-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/best-developer-resources/</guid>
      <description>Below you will find a curated list of resources I have found useful in my endevours designing and developing web applications.
💻 Blogs  Flavio Copes - seemingly endless articles on a wide variety of technical subjects. Most articles are related to web development. 7 Practical Tips for Cheating at Design - a great list of tips to keep in mind when doing web design. They do a fantastic job explaining the concepts, and the article is written to help developers who may struggle with design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe eval alternative in Javascript</title>
      <link>/javascript-safe-eval/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/javascript-safe-eval/</guid>
      <description>A problem I encountered while creating Discord Bot Studio, was allowing users to enter variables which could be evaluated at runtime. Discord Bot Studio is a visual programming tool, so I felt it was important to offer a familiar variable syntax. Ideally, I wanted a user to be able to type a variable using the following notation, and have it be replaced with that variable&amp;rsquo;s value at runtime:
An example would be if I have an object as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add Google Analytics tracking ID to a Hugo site</title>
      <link>/googleanalyticshugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/googleanalyticshugo/</guid>
      <description>For this tutorial I will be assuming you already have a Hugo site setup, and that you have a Google Analytics property with a tracking ID created.
Adding the tracking ID to your site Open your config.toml file, and add a field for googleAnalytics at the top level. Set the value to a string containing the tracking ID.
baseurl = &amp;#34;/&amp;#34; title = &amp;#34;Austin Repp&amp;#34; theme = &amp;#34;ghostwriter&amp;#34; googleAnalytics = &amp;#34;UA-999999999-6&amp;#34; # This is the added line [Params] mainSections = [&amp;#34;post&amp;#34;] intro = true headline = &amp;#34;Austin Repp&amp;#34; Next we will add a Hugo internal template to get the Google Analytics code snippet to be inserted on each of the sites pages when loaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Github Pages custom domain</title>
      <link>/githubpagescustomdomain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/githubpagescustomdomain/</guid>
      <description>For this tutorial I will be assuming you have already setup a site on Github Pages that&amp;rsquo;s being run on the standard USERNAME.github.io domain. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t done so, a quick Google search will yield lots of articles explaining the process. I&amp;rsquo;m using Bluehost as my domain provider, but the steps should be similar for any major domain provider.
Setup in Github repository In your Github repo for the site, navigate to the &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m moving from Wordpress to Hugo</title>
      <link>/wordpresstohugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wordpresstohugo/</guid>
      <description>Why move from Wordpress to Hugo? I created a Wordpress site on Bluehost for my personal/blog site because I thought it would be the easiest way to publish blogs without having to worry about hosting or creating my own site. Even as a developer, I have no interest in spending too much time reinventing the wheel to create a simple blog. After writing just one entry there, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t happy with the solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generating Sales from YouTube micro-influencers</title>
      <link>/youtubemicro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/youtubemicro/</guid>
      <description>For the last few months, I’ve been reaching out to “micro influencers” on YouTube, with the hope of driving targeted traffic to my product, http://discordbotstudio.org. I’m classifying micro influencers as having between 1,000 – 10,000 subscribers on YouTube. The benefit of reaching channels of this size is that they have dedicated audiences based on a certain niche (in my case this is Discord Bots and the creation thereof).
Background Info Discord Bot Studio (DBS) is a visual programming tool I released on Steam on May 12th, 2020 (2 months prior to writing this).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>